Guide to the Sterling Lord Archive 1946-1998 MSS 058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Subseries B: Compiled Author / Publisher Files
    - Berenstains - "It's All In the Family" - McCall's Album (2 of 2), Undated (Box 256, Folder 56)
    - Berenstains - "It's All In the Family" - McCall's Album II, Undated (Box 256, Folder 57)
    - Berenstains - "It's All In the Family" - McCall's Album III, Undated (Box 256, Folder 58)
    - Berenstains - "It's All In the Family" - McCall's Album IV, Undated (Box 256, Folder 59)
    - Berenstains - Jay Franco, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 60)
    - Berenstains - JTG of Nashville, 1989 (Box 256, Folder 61)
    - Berenstains - Just Friends (formerly Pure Goodness), 1992-1994 (Box 256, Folder 62)
    - Berenstains - Kaisei-She - Royalty statements, 1992 (Box 256, Folder 63)
    - Berenstains - Kings Productions, 1992-1993 (Box 256, Folder 64)
    - Berenstains - Knit Mates, 1982-1984 (Box 256, Folder 65)
    - Berenstains - Lee, 1982-1984 (Box 256, Folder 66)
    - Berenstains - Licensing Advantage, 1987-1989 (Box 256, Folder 67)
    - Berenstains - Loom Treasures, 1981 (Box 256, Folder 68)
    - Berenstains - Marimac, 1982-1983 (Box 256, Folder 69)
    - Berenstains - Majdell Mfg., 1982-1983 (Box 256, Folder 70)
    - Berenstains - McCall Patterns, 1984-1986 (Box 256, Folder 71)
    - Berenstains - McDonald's, 1983-1992 (Box 256, Folder 72)
    - Berenstains - McDonald's, c. 1993 (Box 256, Folder 73)
    - Berenstains - McGraw-Hill Royalty statements, 1998 (Box 256, Folder 74)
    - Berenstains - Metropolitan Consol, 1982-1984 (Box 256, Folder 75)
    - Berenstains - Miscellaneous royalty statements, 1983-1991 (Box 256, Folder 76)
    - Berenstains - Mixed royalty statements, Undated (Box 256, Folder 77)
    - Berenstains - Nat'l Paragon, 1982-1984 (Box 256, Folder 78)
    - Berenstains - One Stop Posters, 1987-1989 (Box 256, Folder 79)
    - Berenstains - Outlook Graphics, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 80)
    - Berenstains - Pace Products, 1990-1991 (Box 256, Folder 81)
    - Berenstains - Peninsula Vending, 1993 (Box 256, Folder 82)
    - Berenstains - Plymouth, 1982-1985 (Box 256, Folder 83)
    - Berenstains - Pockets of Learning, 1989-1990 (Box 256, Folder 84)
    - Berenstains - "Premiums", Undated (Box 256, Folder 85)
    - Berenstains - Princess House, 1988-1989 (Box 256, Folder 86)
    - Berenstains - Priss Prints, 1989-1992 (Box 256, Folder 87)
    - Berenstains - Processed Plastic, 1984-1986 (Box 256, Folder 88)
    - Berenstains - Quinn / Brein Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 256, Folder 89)
    - Berenstains - Random House sales / royalty reports, 1994 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Berenstains - Random House sales / royalty reports, 1995 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Berenstains - Random House sales / royalty reports, 1996 (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Berenstains - Random House sales / royalty reports, 1997 (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Berenstains - Random House sales / royalty reports, 1998 (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Berenstains - Rayman / Ridless Products, 1983-1985 (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Berenstains - Romar International, 1991-1993 (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Berenstains - Rose Art, 1990-1992 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Berenstains - Rubin and Roth, 1982-1983 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Berenstains - Russ Berrie, 1983-1986 (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - Berenstains - Salant / Obion, 1982 (Box 257, Folder 11)
    - Berenstains - Scandecor Industries, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - Berenstains - Scholastic royalty statements, 1998 (Box 257, Folder 13)
    - Berenstains - Sears, 1989-1990 (Box 257, Folder 14)
    - Berenstains - Semantodontics, 1990-1992 (Box 257, Folder 15)
    - Berenstains - Stahlwood Toy, 1983-1985 (Box 257, Folder 16)
    - Berenstains - Stampos, 1984-1985 (Box 257, Folder 17)
    - Berenstains - Theme Park, Undated (Box 257, Folder 18)
    - Berenstains - Thermos Div., 1983-1984 (Box 257, Folder 19)
    - Berenstains - Tom-Wat Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 257, Folder 20)
    - Berenstains - Union Underwear, 1989-1991 (Box 257, Folder 21)
    - Berenstains - Universal Ind., 1981 (Box 257, Folder 22)
    - Berenstains - Vanderbilt, 1989-1991 (Box 257, Folder 23)
    - Berenstains - Visionary Products, 1991-1993 (Box 257, Folder 24)
    - Berenstains - West Point / Pepperell, 1982-1984 (Box 257, Folder 25)
    - Client Reader Reports - A-D, 1968 (Box 257, Folder 26)
    - Client Reader Reports - E-H, 1968 (Box 257, Folder 27)
    - Client Reader Reports - I-M, 1968 (Box 257, Folder 28)
    - Client Reader Reports - N-Z (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 257, Folder 29)
    - Client Reader Reports - N-Z (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 257, Folder 30)
    - Client's Biographies A-Z, 1968 (Box 257, Folder 31)
    - Deneger, Claire - "Blessed McGill", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 32)
    - Deneger, Claire - Flynn (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 257, Folder 33)
    - Deneger, Claire - Flynn (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 257, Folder 34)
    - Deneger, Claire - "The Flypaper War", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 35)
    - Deneger, Claire - Gerald Browne Tax Levy, 1976 (Box 257, Folder 36)
    - Deneger, Claire - "Ice and Fire", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 37)
    - Deneger, Claire - Jerry Berger, 1976 (Box 257, Folder 38)
    - Deneger, Claire - "N.Y. Daily News", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 39)
    - Deneger, Claire - "Peers", 1977 (Box 257, Folder 40)
    - Deneger, Claire - "R.I.P", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 41)
    - Deneger, Claire - "Southern Fried Plus Six", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 42)
    - Deneger, Claire - "Thunder Mountain", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 43)
    - Deneger, Claire - "Tom Mix", 1976 (Box 257, Folder 44)
    - Jong, Erica - Anthology: A Woman and Her Work, 1982-1985 (Box 257, Folder 45)
    - Jong, Erica - "At the Edge of the Body", 1978-1980 (Box 257, Folder 46)
    - Jong, Erica - Capri with Jon Fast, 1977 (Box 257, Folder 47)
    - Jong, Erica - Collette - intro, 1976 (Box 257, Folder 48)
    - Jong, Erica - Contracts and legal papers, 1970-1976 (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Jong, Erica - Copyright and permissions, 1975-1983 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Jong, Erica - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Jong, Erica - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Jong, Erica - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Jong, Erica - Drama correspondence, 1984 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Jong, Erica - Fanny Hackabout, 1978-1985 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Jong, Erica - Fanny Hackabout (2 of 2), 1978-1985 (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Jong, Erica - "Fear of Flying" court case decision, 1974-1977 (Box 258, Folder 9)
    - Jong, Erica - Foreign Collections, 1976-1984 (Box 258, Folder 10)
    - Jong, Erica - Four Visions of America, 1977 (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Jong, Erica - "How to Save Your Own Life" deal notes, 1975 (Box 258, Folder 12)
    - Jong, Erica - "How to Save Your Own Life", 1978-1991 (Box 258, Folder 13)
    - Jong, Erica - Megan's Book of Divorce, 1984-1985 (Box 258, Folder 14)
    - Jong, Erica - Ordinary Miracles, 1983-1985 (Box 258, Folder 15)
    - Jong, Erica - "Parachutes and Kisses" contract, 1982 (Box 258, Folder 16)
    - Jong, Erica - Pre SLA, 1973-1984 (Box 258, Folder 17)
    - Jong, Erica - Royalty statements, 1981-1990 (Box 258, Folder 18)
    - Jong, Erica - Spoken Arts Recording contract, 1976 (Box 258, Folder 19)
    - Jong, Erica - Subsidiary Rights, contracts, etc..., Undated (Box 258, Folder 20)
    - Jong, Erica - Tatenbaum, Rae, 1976-1977 (Box 258, Folder 21)
    - Jong, Erica - Three 18th C. Novels / Moll Flanders - Jong intro, 1981 (Box 258, Folder 22)
    - Jong, Erica - Witches, 1979-1986 (Box 258, Folder 23)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "After Me the Deluge" (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 258, Folder 24)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "After Me the Deluge" (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 258, Folder 25)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Beat Generation", Undated (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Beat Generation" manuscript, 1959 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Book of Dreams" manuscript (1 of 2), c. 1960 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Book of Dreams" manuscript (2 of 2), c. 1960 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Book of Sketches" photocopy of original (1 of 2), 1952-1953 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Book of Sketches" photocopy of original (2 of 2), 1952-1953 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence, mixed (2 of 2), Undated (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence, mixed (1 of 2), Undated (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence with Neal Cassady, Undated (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence Apr-Sept. (1 of 3), 1998 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence Apr-Sept. (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence Apr-Sept. (3 of 3), 1998 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Correspondence Oct. - Dec., 1998 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Doctor Sax" original screenplay, 1959 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Dr. Sax and the Great World Snake" film play, Undated (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack - documents relative to Jan Kerouac / Niosia, Neal Gantcher (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - Kerouac, Jack - documents relative to Jan Kerouac / Niosia, Neal Gantcher (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Drama, 1965 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Drama, 1968 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Editor correspondence - Ronna Johnson, Holmes (1 of 2), Undated (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Editor correspondence - Ronna Johnson, Holmes (2 of 2), Undated (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1965 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1972 (Box 261, Folder 16)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1969 (Box 261, Folder 15)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1973 (Box 261, Folder 17)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1974 (Box 261, Folder 18)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1975 (Box 261, Folder 19)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1976 (Box 261, Folder 20)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1978 (Box 261, Folder 21)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspodence, 1979 (Box 261, Folder 22)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign correspondence, 1980 (Box 261, Folder 23)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign rights, 1966 (Box 261, Folder 24)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign rights, 1967 (Box 261, Folder 25)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign rights, 1967 (Box 261, Folder 26)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign rights, 1968 (Box 261, Folder 27)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Foreign rights, 1971 (Box 261, Folder 28)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Jack Kerouac's Letters and Journal of an Egotist" manuscript (1 of 2), 1940 (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Jack Kerouac's Letters and Journal of an Egotist" manuscript (2 of 2), 1940 (Box 259, Folder 15)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "The Journal of an Egotist" manuscript, 1940 (Box 261, Folder 29)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Journal written while writing "On the Road" - photocopy, 1948-1949 (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - Kerouac, Jack - legal issues, Undated (Box 259, Folder 17)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Letters to Sterling Lord - photocopies, 1965-1969 (Box 261, Folder 30)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Mary Cassady" manuscript, Undated (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "On the Road" Zoetrope film, 1990 (Box 259, Folder 18)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Orpheus Emerged" novel, 1945 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Pic" manuscript - photocopy, Undated (Box 259, Folder 19)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Pic" section, 2000 (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Play manuscript, unidentified, Undated (Box 259, Folder 20)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Pomes All Sizes" manuscript, Undated (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Rights correspondence, Undated (Box 259, Folder 21)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Some of the Dharma" manuscript (1 of 3), 1953-1956 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Some of the Dharma" manuscript (2 of 3), 1953-1956 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Some of the Dharma" manuscript (3 of 3), 1953-1956 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1965 (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1967 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1971 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1972 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1973 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1975 (Box 262, Folder 15)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1976 (Box 262, Folder 16)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1977 (Box 262, Folder 17)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1978 (Box 262, Folder 18)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1979 (Box 262, Folder 19)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Sterling Lord correspondence, 1980 (Box 262, Folder 20)
    - Kerouac, Jack - Tearsheets and press, Undated (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Tricycle" - Joanne Akalaitos play, 1998 (Box 259, Folder 22)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Vanity of Doulouz", 1968 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Vanity of Doulouz" master proof (1 of 4), 1967 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Vanity of Doulouz" master proof (2 of 4), 1967 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Vanity of Doulouz" master proof (3 of 4), 1967 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Vanity of Doulouz" master proof (4 of 4), 1967 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Wake Up", 1955 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Wake Up: A Life of the Buddha" manuscript, Undated (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Wake Up" manuscript (1 of 3), 1955 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Wake Up" manuscript (2 of 3), 1955 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack - "Wake Up" manuscript (3 of 3), 1955 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Kesey, Ken - "Twister" sampler, 1996 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Kesey, Ken - various manuscripts, Undated (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Lord, Sterling - "21 Reader Report", Undated (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Lord, Sterling - Addresses, Undated (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Lord, Sterling - Army documents, Undated (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - Lord, Sterling - Arnold Maremont and World Series of Drag Racing photographs, 1955 (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - Lord, Sterling - Artist, photographer, cartoonist contact info and correspondence, 1951 (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Automobile Timing Assn. of America" folder, 1954-1955 (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Lord, Sterling - Beetle Baily cartoon featuring Sterling Lord - original and print, Undated (Box 263, Folder 15)
    - Lord, Sterling - Bills due, 1954 (Box 263, Folder 16)
    - Lord, Sterling - Cage, Perillo, 1950 (Box 263, Folder 17)
    - Lord, Sterling - Catholic Digest, 1954 (Box 263, Folder 18)
    - Lord, Sterling - Christmas card mailing list, Undated (Box 263, Folder 19)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Color TV: Now or Later?", 1950 (Box 263, Folder 20)
    - Lord, Sterling - Correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 263, Folder 21)
    - Lord, Sterling - Correspondence - business, Undated (Box 263, Folder 22)
    - Lord, Sterling - Correspondence - mixed, 1949-1951 (Box 263, Folder 23)
    - Lord, Sterling - Desk calendar, 1955 (Box 263, Folder 24)
    - Lord, Sterling - Early articles, Undated (Box 263, Folder 25)
    - Lord, Sterling - Early Lord and Colbert records, Undated (Box 263, Folder 26)
    - Lord, Sterling - Envelope for 1948 Olympics invitation (Box 263, Folder 27)
    - Lord, Sterling - Family Expense record, 1949 (Box 263, Folder 28)
    - Lord, Sterling - File book A-D, Undated (Box 263, Folder 29)
    - Lord, Sterling - File book E-O, Undated (Box 263, Folder 30)
    - Lord, Sterling - File book P-Z, Undated (Box 263, Folder 31)
    - Lord, Sterling - File book - misc. and unfiled, Undated (Box 263, Folder 32)
    - Lord, Sterling - Follow-up job letters, Undated (Box 263, Folder 33)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Heat and Your Health" pamphlet, 1954 (Box 263, Folder 34)
    - Lord, Sterling - "History of Dr. Scholl", Undated (Box 263, Folder 35)
    - Lord, Sterling - Housing and bills, Undated (Box 263, Folder 36)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Ideas" file - Adventure, Undated (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Ideas" file - Army, Undated (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Ideas" file - Personalities, Undated (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Ideas" file - Self-Help, Undated (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Ideas" file - Sports, Undated (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Lord, Sterling - Income tax return, 1951 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Lord, Sterling - Letters and bulletins, Undated (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Lord, Sterling - Literary Acquisition - "Madonna Red" by James Carroll, 1976 (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Major Accounts of the Public Relations Board", Undated (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Map of New York Subways" from Corn Exchange Bank, Undated (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - Lord, Sterling -Minutes and bylaws of the meetings of SLI Inc., 1956 (Box 264, Folder 11)
    - Lord, Sterling - "My Wife Loves Picasso and Me", Undated (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - Lord, Sterling - New York University legal files, Undated (Box 264, Folder 13)
    - Lord, Sterling - Newspaper and magazine clippings, Undated (Box 264, Folder 14)
    - Lord, Sterling - Park Forest correspondence, 1955 (Box 264, Folder 15)
    - Lord, Sterling - Perillo carbon copies, Undated (Box 264, Folder 16)
    - Lord, Sterling - Perry "Skee" Wolff article, Undated (Box 264, Folder 17)
    - Lord, Sterling - personal, Undated (Box 264, Folder 18)
    - Lord, Sterling - Public Relations Board, Undated (Box 264, Folder 19)
    - Lord, Sterling - Publishing, general info, Undated (Box 264, Folder 20)
    - Lord, Sterling - Radio Writers Guild, 1947-1952 (Box 264, Folder 21)
    - Lord, Sterling - Representation file, Undated (Box 264, Folder 22)
    - Lord, Sterling - Research - Segura, Undated (Box 264, Folder 23)
    - Lord, Sterling - Resume, 1952 (Box 264, Folder 24)
    - Lord, Sterling - Salary / voucher slips, 1951-1952 (Box 264, Folder 25)
    - Lord, Sterling - Stock certificates, Undated (Box 264, Folder 26)
    - Lord, Sterling - Tennis research, Undated (Box 264, Folder 27)
    - Lord, Sterling - Text books, Undated (Box 264, Folder 28)
    - Lord, Sterling - TRUE Magazine, 1950-1951 (Box 264, Folder 29)
    - Lord, Sterling - TV and Radio file, Undated (Box 264, Folder 30)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Weekend" European magazine, 1947-1949 (Box 264, Folder 31)
    - Lord, Sterling - "Yale Club", Undated (Box 264, Folder 32)
    - Lord, Sterling - Yale Club story for the Racquet, Undated (Box 264, Folder 33)
    - Mixed Author Files - Ameche, Don - "Many Happy Returns", Undated (Box 264, Folder 34)
    - Mixed Author Files - Aramony, William - "One Person at a Time", Undated (Box 264, Folder 35)
    - Mixed Author Files - Beach, Edward - "The Last 50 Years", Undated (Box 264, Folder 36)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Arena Show, 1991 (Box 264, Folder 37)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - "The Art of Stan and Jan", Undated (Box 264, Folder 38)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - "Billy and the Berenstain Bears", Undated (Box 264, Folder 39)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Circle Fine Art, Undated (Box 264, Folder 40)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - financial, Undated (Box 264, Folder 41)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - financial, Undated (Box 264, Folder 42)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - financial / licensing, Undated (Box 264, Folder 43)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - "First Time Games", Undated (Box 264, Folder 44)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Movie treatment, 1984 (Box 264, Folder 45)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - QVC, 1993 (Box 264, Folder 46)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - royalty statements, Undated (Box 264, Folder 47)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Sega, Undated (Box 264, Folder 48)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Spain, 1990 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Western Book 'n' Tape, Undated (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Western Publisher copyright cert., Undated (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Mixed Author Files - Berenstains - Western Publishing direct mail, Undated (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Mixed Author Files - Canning, Peter - "Pleasantville", Undated (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Mixed Author Files - Cohen, Nathan - "Animal Talk", Undated (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - Mixed Author Files - Dekmejian, R.H. - "Saddam", 1991 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Mixed Author Files - Dietl, Beau - treatment, Undated (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Mixed Author Files - Dogs, Joe - treatment file, Undated (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Mixed Author Files - Donaldson, Scott - "Archibald Macleish...", Undated (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Mixed Author Files - Drury, Bob - "Hildy Rodger's Story", Undated (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - Mixed Author Files - Durham, Guy - "Catfish Queen", Undated (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Mixed Author Files - Fast, Howard - "Writing About a Woman", Undated (Box 265, Folder 13)
    - Mixed Author Files - Fiske, Ted - "Business Schools", "Admissions", Undated (Box 265, Folder 14)
    - Mixed Author Files - Gent, Peter - "North Dallas", Undated (Box 265, Folder 15)
    - Mixed Author Files - Gent, Peter and Stabler - "Dirty Little Secrets", Undated (Box 265, Folder 16)
    - Mixed Author Files - Gent, Peter - "NFL Sports Injuries Articles", Undated (Box 265, Folder 17)
    - Mixed Author Files - Goddard, Donald - "Out of Control", Undated (Box 265, Folder 18)
    - Mixed Author Files - Goodwin, Doris - "Franklin and Eleanor", Undated (Box 265, Folder 19)
    - Mixed Author Files - Greenfield, Casey, Undated (Box 265, Folder 20)
    - Mixed Author Files - Greenya, John - "Bembenek", Undated (Box 265, Folder 21)
    - Mixed Author Files - Gross, Leonard - "Up and Down", 1991 (Box 265, Folder 22)
    - Mixed Author Files - Gross, Leonard - "Maraveem", Undated (Box 265, Folder 23)
    - Mixed Author Files - Gross, Leonard - "Chet Forte Story", Undated (Box 265, Folder 24)
    - Mixed Author Files - Gross, Leonard - "Final Choices", Undated (Box 265, Folder 25)
    - Mixed Author Files - Hagstrom, Jerry - "The New Bosses", Undated (Box 265, Folder 26)
    - Mixed Author Files - Hall, Richard - "Tips for Mighty", Undated (Box 265, Folder 27)
    - Mixed Author Files - IFP, 1993 (Box 265, Folder 28)
    - Mixed Author Files - Kerouac, Jack - "Selected Letters of Jack Kerouac", 1992 (Box 265, Folder 29)
    - Mixed Author Files - LaBroque, Ron - "Going Over", Undated (Box 265, Folder 30)
    - Mixed Author Files - Leonard, George - "The American Beat", Undated (Box 265, Folder 31)
    - Mixed Author Files - Leonard, George - "Stealth Bomber", 1990 (Box 265, Folder 32)
    - Mixed Author Files - Levinson, William - "Requiem for a Gentleman", 1989 (Box 265, Folder 33)
    - Mixed Author Files - Lucas, W. Scott - "Suez Crisis", Undated (Box 265, Folder 34)
    - Mixed Author Files - Manley, Dexter - "Dexter Manley Story", Undated (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Mixed Author Files - Morrow, Lance - "Africa Book", 1989 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Mixed Author Files - Morrow, Lance - "Are Men That Bad?", 1994 (Box 266, Folder 3)